https://www.portrait4u.co.uk/privacy-poilcy

Privacy PolicyThe privacy of the information you provide to us is important and this statement is intended to inform and reassure you of our commitment to respecting your privacy.
This applies to all information on this website. On some pages, you can order products or make requests The personal information collected at these pages may include:
Name
Company name
Address
Email address
Phone number(s)
We use the information you provide about yourself to provide you with information or to complete an order. We never share this information with third parties apart from what is necessary to answer a request or to complete an order. The same applies to information you provide about someone else.
Your return email address is used to reply to you and your email address is not shared with outside parties
We may use Google Analytics or similar software to record information about the way our site is accessed and used by visitors. This software does not and cannot identify personal information.
We never use or share the personal information provided to us online other than described above without your permission and without also offering you the choice to opt out.
We DO NOT collect:
Credit Card or Debit Card Information from this website. Any sales made directly from this website are performed through PayPal who do not disclose credit/debit card information to us.
We may tell you what personal information we hold by sending an email. This procedure helps us verify your identity and safeguard your information. At your request we will either correct any errors or remove your information from our system.
